Looks like human bones were dug up.
=Medical Examiner Dr. Qin: Bones of the Past=
=Episode 1=
The dorsal rim of the pubic symphysis
has formed and become prominent.
The ventral rim
shows signs of degeneration.
Combined with the condition
of the auricular surface,
the deceased was female,
approximately 35 years old.
Her pelvis shows evidence of childbirth.
She had given birth
to at least one child.
The sternum near the heart
shows signs of repeated cutting
with a sharp instrument,
leaving parallel incisions.
The cut surfaces
of the bone are flat and smooth.
They appear to be tool marks left behind
after the chest was cut open
and the heart removed.
Her heart
was most likely removed.
There are multiple
comminuted fractures of the skull,
concentrated at the top.
Note the direction
of these fracture lines
and the order in which they overlap.
The wounds are consistent in shape.
They're all roughly circular depressions
with radiating fractures.
They were caused by blows
from the same type of round,
hammer-like object.
Based on where the major
fracture lines terminate
and how the wounds overlap,
the victim sustained
at least ten such fatal blows.
Every blow
was delivered with full force.
(Chen Shiyu, Medical Examiner)
You can hardly
(of Longfan City Public Security Bureau)
even call this murder.
This was a sadistic killing.
(Qin Ming, Medical Examiner
of Longfan City Public Security Bureau)
Based on the erosion of the bones
and the degree of collagen loss,
the remains were likely
buried about 30 years ago.
30 years ago would put it in 1990.
I'll run a DNA test first
and see if we can identify her.
(Riverside Skeleton Case)
We've identified the riverside remains.
According to Longfan City's
missing persons records from 1990,
the deceased was Liu Yan.
(Lin Tao, Deputy Captain of Criminal Investigation)
She was 35 when she disappeared.
(of Longfan City Public Security Bureau)
She was an accountant
at Longfan Urban Construction Group
and had a daughter.
She was reported missing in May 1990.
Based on all the information,
these remains
belong to Liu Yan,
who disappeared 30 years ago.
- Don't push.
- Is it our turn yet?
(Liu Yan, Accountant
of Longfan Urban Construction Group)
One at a time.
Everyone will get one.
(Longfan Urban Construction Group)
Everyone, I know
(Investment Conference)
all of you here today
have put everything you own into this.
Some of you
may still have your doubts.
But what you're about to witness
(Huo Qicheng, General Manager)
is a miracle beyond your wildest dreams!
(of Longfan Urban Construction Group)
- Yes!
If you invest 10,000 yuan today,
(Jin Juan, Huo Qicheng's Wife)
then by this time next year,
you'll see returns of ten
or even twenty times that amount.
But if you hesitate
for even a second today,
tomorrow, you'll only
be watching others get rich
while you're
left regretting your decision.
Count me in! I want in too!
(In 1990,)
(Longfan Urban Construction Group
suddenly rose to prominence,)
(fueling dreams
of overnight riches across Longfan.)
(But those dreams
were shattered in an instant.)
(Tens of millions in investment funds
mysteriously vanished,)
(leaving the entire city devastated.)
(Rumor had it
that the money had been transferred)
(and squandered.)
(But the group's
Chief Financial Officer, Liu Yan, knew)
(the fortune was still in Longfan.)
(If the secret ever got out,)
(it would cost her life.)
(Liang Chao, Deputy General Manager
of Longfan Urban Construction Group)
Hello?
Liu Yan.
Get to the office right away.
It's urgent.
Help me get the money
and you can stay on
as Chief Financial Officer.
If I go to prison,
I'm taking you down with me.
Give us our money back!
Fraudsters!
- Give us our money back!
- Fraudsters!
(Doctor Lin Luoxia, Qin Ming's Mother)
Son.
Happy birthday.
Why did you buy such a big cake again?
Mom,
I don't eat cake.
There's your father too.
Every year,
I always save a share for him.
The three of us
will always be together.
Ming.
(Qin Tian, Criminal Investigation Captain)
Mom and Dad wish you a happy birthday.
(of Longfan City Public Security Bureau)
Son,
happy birthday.
(Young Qin Ming, Qin Tian's Son)
♪Happy birthday to you♪
Mom,
Dad died in
the fundraising case 30 years ago.
He'd want both of us to live well,
not to keep
living in the past like this.
I know you still can't let him go,
but shouldn't we...
That's right.
I haven't cut your dad's cake yet.
I'll go cut him a slice right now.
Sunspot groups
can produce intense solar flares.
This is a typical form
of solar activity,
usually accompanied by X-ray bursts,
coronal mass ejections,
and other phenomena.
These may affect communications
and satellites on Earth.
Ming,
why are you still awake?
I know you're in here playing
with the walkie-talkie.
Dad.
If you can hear me, respond.
Dad's here.
Ming,
do you like
the birthday present I gave you?
Now I can talk to you anytime.
Ming,
remember this.
This is our private channel.
You have to keep it secret, okay?
Now hurry up and go to sleep.
Do you hear me?
You...
You just called me Ming.
Who are you?
How can you use this walkie-talkie?
How can you use this channel?
You're Qin Tian,
Captain of Criminal Investigation
at the Longfan City Public Security Bureau.
You know me?
Captain Qin.
This walkie-talkie
was the birthday present
you gave your son, Qin Ming,
for his fifth birthday, right?
Who are you?
What do you want?
I'm a police officer.
Stay away from my son.
I'm Qin Ming.
Qin Tian,
where are you?
Don't mess around.
You don't mess with the police.
I can track you down.
Captain Qin,
at the Public Security Bureau,
you're known as a walking map.
There's not a street or alley in Longfan
that you don't know.
Whenever you discover a new road,
you go home
and add it to your hand-drawn map.
That map is one of a kind.
Just now,
you spilled a drop
of blue ink on the map,
didn't you?
You've been watching me?
You just told me you're Ming,
but my son is only five.
You're a young man.
How could you possibly be Ming?
Qin.
Qin, can you hear me? Qin.
Captain Qin.
Can you hear me?
(Detective Qin Tian pursued a suspect)
(and was killed
in the line of duty aboard a train)
Stop!
Dad!
Run!
There's a bomb!
May 20th.
(Detective Qin Tian pursued a suspect)
(and was killed in the line of duty aboard a train)
(If Dad had known about the bomb sooner,)
(May 21, 1990)
(maybe he wouldn't have died.)
♪The old walkie-talkie I treasure♪
♪The birthday surprise
you gave me that year♪
♪Its buttons worn
and weathered with time♪
♪Still echoing your words,
"Be brave and keep moving on"♪
♪The old train rolled over
our reluctance to part♪
♪You waved goodbye
and faded into the night♪
♪I used to think
we'd always have more time♪
♪But that goodbye
became the last♪
♪I carry the warmth you left behind♪
♪Making my way
through every door in life♪
♪Whenever a train
whistle sounds at night♪
♪I suddenly
long to call out to you♪
♪Can you hear me?♪
♪Let the old receiver
carry the words I never said♪
♪I've taken on
both your duty and your love♪
♪This train has no return, and when I
look back, you're no longer waiting♪
♪After all these years♪
♪How I wish I could
talk to you just one more time♪
♪And tell you♪
♪I haven't let you down♪